const DATA = [
    {
        "front": "ser",
        "back": "to be (essential/permanent quality)"
    },
    {
        "front": "haber",
        "back": "to have (to do something, auxiliary verb)"
    },
    {
        "front": "estar",
        "back": "to be (health, location, state)"
    },
    {
        "front": "tener",
        "back": "to have"
    },
    {
        "front": "hacer",
        "back": "to do, to make"
    },
    {
        "front": "poder",
        "back": "to be able to, can"
    },
    {
        "front": "decir",
        "back": "to say, to tell"
    },
    {
        "front": "ir",
        "back": "to go"
    },
    {
        "front": "ver",
        "back": "to see"
    },
    {
        "front": "dar",
        "back": "to give"
    },
    {
        "front": "saber",
        "back": "to know (information)"
    },
    {
        "front": "querer",
        "back": "to want, to love"
    },
    {
        "front": "llegar",
        "back": "to arrive, to come, to reach"
    },
    {
        "front": "pasar",
        "back": "to pass, to spend (time), to happen"
    },
    {
        "front": "deber",
        "back": "to owe, to must, should, ought to"
    },
    {
        "front": "poner",
        "back": "to put, to place, to set"
    },
    {
        "front": "parecer",
        "back": "to seem, to appear"
    },
    {
        "front": "quedar",
        "back": "to stay, to remain"
    },
    {
        "front": "creer",
        "back": "to believe"
    },
    {
        "front": "hablar",
        "back": "to speak"
    },
    {
        "front": "llevar",
        "back": "to carry, to bring"
    },
    {
        "front": "dejar",
        "back": "to leave, to abandon, to let, allow"
    },
    {
        "front": "seguir",
        "back": "to follow, continue"
    },
    {
        "front": "encontrar",
        "back": "to find, to encounter"
    },
    {
        "front": "llamar",
        "back": "to call, to name"
      },
      {
        "front": "venir",
        "back": "to come"
      },
      {
        "front": "pensar",
        "back": "to think"
      },
      {
        "front": "salir",
        "back": "to leave, to go out"
      },
      {
        "front": "volver",
        "back": "to return, to go back"
      },
      {
        "front": "tomar",
        "back": "to take, to drink"
      },
      {
        "front": "conocer",
        "back": "to know (people, places)"
      },
      {
        "front": "vivir",
        "back": "to live"
      },
      {
        "front": "sentir",
        "back": "to feel, regret"
      },
      {
        "front": "tratar",
        "back": "to treat, to handle"
      },
      {
        "front": "mirar",
        "back": "to watch, to look at"
      },
      {
        "front": "contar",
        "back": "to count, to relate to, to tell"
      },
      {
        "front": "empezar",
        "back": "to begin, to start"
      },
      {
        "front": "esperar",
        "back": "to wait for, to hope"
      },
      {
        "front": "buscar",
        "back": "to search for, to hope"
      },
      {
        "front": "existir",
        "back": "to exist"
      },
      {
        "front": "entrar",
        "back": "to enter, to go in, to come in"
      },
      {
        "front": "trabajar",
        "back": "to work"
      },
      {
        "front": "escribir",
        "back": "to write"
      },
      {
        "front": "perder",
        "back": "to lose"
      },
      {
        "front": "producir",
        "back": "to produce"
      },
      {
        "front": "ocurrir",
        "back": "to occur, happen"
      },
      {
        "front": "entender",
        "back": "to understand"
      },
      {
        "front": "pedir",
        "back": "to request, to ask for"
      },
      {
        "front": "recibir",
        "back": "to receive, to welcome, to greet"
      },
      {
        "front": "recordar",
        "back": "to remember, to remind"
      },
      {
        "front": "terminar",
        "back": "to finish, to end"
      },
      {
        "front": "permitir",
        "back": "to permit, to allow"
      },
      {
        "front": "aparecer",
        "back": "to appear, show up"
      },
      {
        "front": "conseguir",
        "back": "to get, to obtain"
      },
      {
        "front": "comenzar",
        "back": "to begin, to start, to commence"
      },
      {
        "front": "servir",
        "back": "to serve"
      },
      {
        "front": "sacar",
        "back": "to take out, to stick out"
      },
      {
        "front": "necesitar",
        "back": "to need, to require"
      },
      {
        "front": "mantener",
        "back": "to maintain, to get"
      },
      {
        "front": "resultar",
        "back": "to turn out (to be)"
      },
      {
        "front": "leer",
        "back": "to read"
      },
      {
        "front": "caer",
        "back": "to fall"
      },
      {
        "front": "cambiar",
        "back": "to change"
      },
      {
        "front": "presentar",
        "back": "to introduce"
      },
      {
        "front": "crear",
        "back": "to create, to make"
      },
      {
        "front": "abrir",
        "back": "to open"
      },
      {
        "front": "considerar",
        "back": "to consider"
      },
      {
        "front": "o√≠r",
        "back": "to hear"
      },
      {
        "front": "acabar",
        "back": "to finish, to end"
      },
      {
        "front": "convertir",
        "back": "to convert, to change"
      },
      {
        "front": "ganar",
        "back": "to win, to gain, to earn, to get, to acquire"
      },
      {
        "front": "formar",
        "back": "to form, to shape, to fashion, to make"
      },
      {
        "front": "traer",
        "back": "to bring, to get, to fetch, to carry"
      },
      {
        "front": "partir",
        "back": "to divide, to leave"
      },
      {
        "front": "morir",
        "back": "to die"
      },
      {
        "front": "aceptar",
        "back": "to accept, to approve, to agree to"
      },
      {
        "front": "realizar",
        "back": "to achieve, to attain, to accomplish"
      },
      {
        "front": "suponer",
        "back": "to suppose"
      },
      {
        "front": "comprender",
        "back": "to understand, to comprehend"
      },
      {
        "front": "lograr",
        "back": "to , to obtain, to achieve, to attain"
      },
      {
        "front": "explicar",
        "back": "to explain"
      },
      {
        "front": "preguntar",
        "back": "to ask, to inquire"
      },
      {
        "front": "tocar",
        "back": "to touch, to play (an instrument)"
      },
      {
        "front": "reconocer",
        "back": "to recognize"
      },
      {
        "front": "estudiar",
        "back": "to study"
      },
      {
        "front": "alcanzar",
        "back": "to reach, to catch up"
      },
      {
        "front": "nacer",
        "back": "to be born"
      },
      {
        "front": "dirigir",
        "back": "to direct"
      },
      {
        "front": "correr",
        "back": "to run"
      },
      {
        "front": "utilizar",
        "back": "to use, to utilize"
      },
      {
        "front": "pagar",
        "back": "to pay, to pay for"
      },
      {
        "front": "ayudar",
        "back": "to help"
      },
      {
        "front": "gustar",
        "back": "to please, to be pleasing"
      },
      {
        "front": "jugar",
        "back": "to play (a game or sort)"
      },
      {
        "front": "escuchar",
        "back": "to listen, to hear"
      },
      {
        "front": "cumplir",
        "back": "to fulfil, to carry out"
      },
      {
        "front": "ofrecer",
        "back": "to offer"
      },
      {
        "front": "descubrir",
        "back": "to discover"
      },
      {
        "front": "levantar",
        "back": "to raise, to lift"
      },
      {
        "front": "intentar",
        "back": "to try, to attempt"
      }
]